kingsroadmerch.com 2011-06-23

# Privacy Policy | Kings Road Merch

## Privacy Policy

EPITAPH recognizes and respects the privacy of users who visit this Site and has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. We are committed to providing you with services that you are confident in using. We want you to be fully informed about the information that we collect, why we collect it, and with whom we share it. It is our hope that, after reading this notice, you will understand our commitment to privacy and be confident that we will use your information responsibly. By accessing this Site or otherwise using EPITAPH's services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy will change from time to time to reflect changes in how we do business and changes in services available to you through our Site. We show the effective date at the end of the Privacy Policy. You may access the most recent policy by clicking on the "Privacy Policy" link on our home page. We encourage you to check our privacy policy from time to time.

We collect and use information about you where we reasonably believe it will help us administer our site or provide products, services or other opportunities to you. Among other things, we use the information we learn about you to help us personalize and improve the experience you have with us, to respond to your requests and to communicate with you. The types of information we collect, retain and use include the following:

### Site Use Information

In general you are free to visit our Site anonymously, without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers may track and collect the domain names and IP addresses of visitors and this information may be aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, etc. We may use this information ("behavior profiles") to measure the use of our Site and to improve the content we offer. We may share with third parties experiential information or other data which does not personally identify users of our Site. This might include artist, product or service preferences of all visitors to our Site, for example.

### Personally Identifiable Information

You are not required to register in order to access our Site or to browse in the EPITAPH Store. However, you may choose to register on our Site to be able to access to certain portions of our Site by providing a username and password (which you select) along with certain personally identifiable information including your email address and ZIP code ("Personally Identifiable Information"). If you choose to subscribe to our mailing list we will collect your email address and ZIP code. You can subscribe to our mailing list to receive periodic newsletters about our artists without registering on the Site. The information we collect helps us to identify you and to personalize our services to you. When you register on our Site your email address, username and password may be linked and they will be stored on the Company's servers in the United States or the servers of our third party providers. If you send us an email, our email server will store your email address for a limited amount of time and then delete it. If you make a purchase at the EPITAPH Store, your name, email address and telephone number may be linked and may be stored on the Company’s servers in the United States or the servers of our third party providers. EPITAPH does not collect any other information about you on line which would personally identify you other than described in this Privacy Policy.

### The EPITAPH Web Store

The EPITAPH Web Store is operated by Kings Road Merch, a division of EPITAPH. Additional technical support may be provided by other third party vendors. If you make a purchase at the EPITAPH Web Store you will be providing information to Kings Road Merch and to EPITAPH. You are not required to register to shop, but must provide billing and shipping information if you decide to make a purchase. For your security, we do not store your credit card information, your billing information or your shipping information, this information is only used to process your order. This means that you will have to provide this information whenever you make a purchase at our Store. We may retain your name, telephone number and email address unless you tell us not to. After you make a purchase you will receive an email confirming your purchase and inviting you to join the Epitaph or Kings Road Merch mailing lists. You can choose to join or to opt-out as described in the email. [EITHER: Kings Road Merch has a separate privacy policy which may be different from ours. Please review their privacy policy at __[link?]_____.] OR [Kings Road Merch has agreed to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy.]

### Security

Information you provide through our Store is protected by SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) security technology to encrypt information while it is in transmission over the internet, but any information you provide us on the balance of the Site or by email is unencrypted. Data transmission over the internet is never 100% secure.

While we take steps to protect your personal information and keep it secure, you also play a role in protecting your information. You can help to maintain the security of your online transactions by not sharing your user name, email address, credit card or other information with anyone. We cannot guaranty the security of any information you provide us, and therefore you do so at your own risk.

### Community Forums

This Site may make available to you chat rooms, bulletin boards, forums or other community functions. Please be aware that any information you post in any of these community areas immediately becomes public information and EPITAPH is not responsible to protect that information from access by third parties. As a result, please use caution before posting any personal information in any of these community forums. You use community forums at your own risk.

### How We Use Your Information

By providing Personally Identifiable Information to us, you explicitly agree to our collection and use of that information as described in this Privacy Policy. We may use your Personally Identifiable Information to respond to your inquiries, to contact you regarding special announcements, to send you our newsletter, to let you know about artists, products or services which may be of interest to you, or for other purposes. We use your ZIP code to provide information about events in your area. To help us determine whether you have received an email from us, and to help us make emails more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation that you have opened an email from us.

### Cookies

Like many web sites we use "cookies" to identify your computer and to enable us to remember your password, to help us identify the portions of our Site that may be the most relevant for your needs, and to help us identify other products or services that may be of interest to you or others. A cookie is a small piece of information that a web site can store on your web browser and then retrieve at a later time. We use cookies to track the portions of our Site you visit. However, we do NOT use cookies to examine your surfing behavior before or after you leave our Site. There are products commercially available that are designed to help you disable cookies. Although we want you to be aware that such products exist, please note that if you choose to use them we will not be able to provide you with a personalized service, and it may result in certain features and services not being available to you.

### Sharing Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may share with third parties information, including behavior profiles, which is based on our experiential or other data which does not personally identify any of our users. We may share this non-personally identifiable information with our agents, outside vendors or third parties who perform functions on our behalf (such as providing marketing or customer assistance).

### Sharing Personally Identifiable Information

We are not in the business of selling, renting or sharing your Personally Identifiable Information to or with others. While we may share your Personally Identifiable Information with our affiliated companies, we do not reveal Personally Identifiable Information about you to unaffiliated third parties, unless: (1) you request or authorize it; (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); or (5) the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, etc.).

### Your California Privacy Rights

EPITAPH may disclose your personal information to our affiliated companies for their use in marketing to you unless you tell us not to. In order to opt out of such sharing or for further information, please contact us at __________. [Note: California law requires that if you share information with any other company – affiliated or unaffiliated – that they will use to directly market to that person, then you must be prepared to disclose to your customers (on their request) the names and address of the recipients of that information and the type of information disclosed. If you provide an “opt-out” of sharing for direct marketing purposes, then your response to requesting customers only has to be that they can opt-out of such sharing with an explanation of how to opt out.

### Child Privacy

Because of the nature of our business, our products and services are not designed to appeal to children, and therefore we do not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children. Our terms and conditions of use require that any registration may only be made by those over the age of 16. By using our services, you are representing that you are at least 16 years of age or have the permission from a parent or legal guardian to use our service. If we know that information is being provided by a child under the age of 16, we will not collect the information without parental consent or parent notification, which will include the opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information or to prevent the child's participation in the activity. Without parental consent, online information will only be used to respond to an unsolicited request and for no other purposes. We recognize that protecting children's identities and privacy online is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with both the online industry and with parents. We encourage parents or guardians to monitor the use of this Site by children to insure that they are not exposed to material that the parent or guardian may find objectionable. Parents are also encouraged to use parental control capabilities within their internet software to assist in their efforts to limit access to certain sites.

### Access to Your Information

You may choose to remove your email address from our mailing list or to cancel your registration by checking the "Unsubscribe" box on the registration form or on the mailing list subscription form. If you believe that any of the information is incorrect, please simply "Unsubscribe" on either the registration or mailing list form and re-subscribe with the correct information.

If you make a purchase at the EPITAPH Store you may view your order receipt only by entering your email address and the order number. If you do not want your information shared for marketing purposes please contact us at _____.

While we take reasonable measures to prevent the loss or misuse of the information that you provide to us, including but not limited to, your Personally Identifiable Information, due to factors beyond our control, we do not guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information or any other information collected by us will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or other third parties or from other criminal activities.

### Linked Sites or Other Parties

EPITAPH's Site may contain links to other sites such as our affiliates and third parties. This Privacy Policy only addresses EPITAPH's use and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site, if any. While we try to link only to sites that share our standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites, although we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites.

### Terms Of Use, Notices And Changes To This Privacy Policy

As our business changes from time to time, this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use are expected to change from time to time, and we reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use at any time. The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect at the time of use. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or statements regarding our privacy practices. We may post any changes to the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use on our Site. We encourage you to check our Site frequently to see the current Policy in effect and any changes that may have been made to it. By choosing to visit our Site you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use (incorporated herein by reference) or any other agreement we have with you, will be governed by the law of the State of California. In the event of any conflict between the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, then the Terms of Use shall control. You also agree to arbitrate such disputes and to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Use or other agreement we have with you.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact the Company at [info@epitaph.com](mailto:info@epitaph.com) or write to:

**EPITAPH**  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
2798 Sunset Blvd.  
Los Angeles, CA 90026

We welcome your questions and comments.

Effective Date. This Privacy Policy is effective as of ___, 2008
